<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Welkin Works</title>
    <link>https://welkinworks.co/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Welkin Works</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://welkinworks.co/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Software Development</title>
      <link>https://welkinworks.co/services/software-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://welkinworks.co/services/software-development/</guid>
      <description>Consulting and development of modern cloud-based applications.
We specialize in cloud-based containerized applications running in cloud platforms such as Kubernetes, and RedHat OpenShift. Some of our work include:
  Design and implementation of database systems, for both OLTP and OLAP purposes.
  Design and implementation of distributed systems based on microservices.
  API Gateways / load-balancers.
  For more information, and a free consultation, please feel free to contact us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevOps</title>
      <link>https://welkinworks.co/services/devops/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://welkinworks.co/services/devops/</guid>
      <description>A lightweight yet powerful stack for early startups.
Having a good DevOps stack is one of the most important aspects of early startups. Let us handle your code-to-production pipeline, and you can focus on what&#39;s important, your product. Our custom DevOps stack includes:
Gogs Every pipeline starts with your code. Gogs is a self-hosted alternative to enterprise GitHub and Bitbucket solutions.
Drone The heart of our DevOps stack, it takes care of testing and converting your code into artifacts that can be used into following stages of the pipeline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://welkinworks.co/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 17:01:34 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://welkinworks.co/contact/</guid>
      <description>Feel free to contact us anytime about any of our services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://welkinworks.co/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://welkinworks.co/about/</guid>
      <description>Our main goal as a company is to make you successful.
Your partner during early stages There&#39;s hundreds of tools, techniques, libraries, and frameworks. It is virtually impossible for anyone to not get overwhelmed when starting a new project.
Our tools can be yours One of the most overlooked aspects by new early startups is their tooling. However, investing time in useful tooling can make your team faster, and your milestones too.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>